Guide to the Marilyn Skolnick Papers, 1952-2009 AIS.2001.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Organizations, 1977-2002; IV.
  - Sierra Club, 1981-2001; 3.
    - Schmidt, Jeff, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Scorecard Committee, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Serving on Committees, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Sierran, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Skolnick, Marilyn, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Skolnick, Marilyn, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Skolnick, Marilyn, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Solid Waste Committee, undated (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - SPEL, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - SPRAWL, 1995-1999 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - SPRAWL, 1997-1999 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - SPRAWL, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - SPRAWL, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - SPRAWL, undated (Box 68, Folder 19-21)
    - Spotlight, 1993-1996 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - State Legislature Questionnaire, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - State Parks Policy, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Summaries, undated (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Sustainable Communities, undated (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Testimony, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Testimony, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Transportation, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Transportation, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Transportation, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Transportation, 1993-1997 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Transportation, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 33-34)
    - Transportation, 1996-1997 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Transportation, 1996-1999 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Transportation, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Transportation Subcommittee, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Treasure's Report, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - Urban Environment, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - Urban Environment Committee, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - Urban Environment Committee, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 42)
    - Urban Transportation Issues, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 43)
    - Wabash Tunnel, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 44)
    - Water, undated (Box 68, Folder 45)
    - Western Pennsylvania Voluntary Toxic Reduction, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 46)
    - Wetlands, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 47)
    - Wetlands, 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 48)
    - Wetlands, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 49)
    - Wildlife, undated (Box 68, Folder 50)
- Governmental Issues/Legislation, 1983-2006; V.
  Marilyn Skolnick was involved with various organizations concerning environmental and transportation issues throughout Pennsylvania. In order for Skolnick to best address these issues, she became involved with candidates during election periods to interview them on their views on these pressing topics. In addition to her active involvement on governmental affairs and elections, Skolnick was also interested in campaigning for peace. She did this by participating in the Peace Links organization. This series mainly addresses candidates' opinions on transportation, environmental, and labor affairs in the state of Pennsylvania; and Marilyn Skolnick's involvement with the Peace Links campaign.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject and dates from 1983 to 2006.
  - Allegheny County Department of Law, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 51)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics News, 1994-1999 (Box 68, Folder 52)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics News, 1996-2001 (Box 68, Folder 53)
  - Campaign Clips, 1996-1997 (Box 68, Folder 54)
  - Campaign Financing, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 55)
  - Campaign Materials, 1989-1992 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Materials, 1990-1992 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Materials, 1990-1992 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Questions, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Results, undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Candidate List for Municipal Primary, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Common Cause, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Common Cause, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Congress, William Coyne, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Department of Economic Development, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Economic Planning and Development, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Economic Development Committee, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Economic and Community Development, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Economic Development and Plan, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Elections, Mayor and Judge, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Email Questionnaire, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Federal Registry, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Grant Information, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - House/Senate Bill Analysis, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - House of Representatives Transcript, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Joint Economic Committee, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Keystone Opportunity Zones, undated (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Labor, 1994-1995 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Labor, 1995-1998 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Leadership Pittsburgh XIII, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Week in Review, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Week in Review, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Update, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Review, 1997-2001 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - MSA Labor Market Newsletters, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous, 1996-1999 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous, 1997-1999 (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Newsclippings, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Newsletters, 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - NAFTA, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Nuclear Disarmament, 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Nuclear Disarmament, 1998-2000 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Peace Links, Beijing Conference, 1996 (Box 72, Video 1)
  - Peace Links, Beyond Beijing: the International Women's Movement, 1996 (Box 72, Video 2, Unknown item 2)
  - Peace Links, Dark Circle: Better World Society, 1987 (Box 72, Video 3)
  - Peace Links, Ernie Tannie Memorial Tape, undated (Box 72, Video 4)
  - Peace Links, Hasidism in America, undated (Box 72, Video 5)
  - Peace Links, National Defense: Behind the Frontier, undated (Box 72, Video 6)
  - Peace Links, Nairobi: It's Up to Us, 1985 (Box 72, Video 7)
  - Peace Links, Politics: Go For It, 1987 (Box 72, Video 8)
  - Peace Links, Quest for Peace: Clark Clifford, undated (Box 73, Video 1)
  - Peace Links, Quest for Peace: Robert Muller, undated (Box 73, Video 2)
  - Peace Links, Sadako and the Thousand Purple Cranes, 1991 (Box 73, Video 3)
  - Peace Links, War: To What End, 1988 (Box 73, Video 4)
  - Peace Links, War: America's Nuclear Shame, March 13, 1994 (Box 73, Video 5)
  - Peace Links, War: A Step Away from War, undated (Box 73, Video 6-7)
  - Peace Links, Westminster Event, 1995 (Box 73, Video 8)
  - Peace Links, Women Against Nuclear War, 1983-1991 (Box 74, Oversize 1)
  - Peace Links, Workshop Negotiation, 1986 (Box 73, Video 9)
  - Peace Links, Visit to Russia, 1987 (Box 74, Oversize 2)
  - Pennsylvania Bulletin, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - Pennsylvania Division Organization, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Pennsylvania Economy League, 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 40)
  - Pennsylvania for Modern Courts, 1994-1995 (Box 69, Folder 41)
  - Pennsylvania Labor Force Monthly Statistical Analysis, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 42)
  - Pennsylvania Labor Force Monthly Statistical Analysis, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 43)
  - Pennsylvania Labor Force, 1998-2001 (Box 69, Folder 44)
  - Pennsylvania Senate Wrap-Ups, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 45)
  - Politics, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 46)
  - Political Visits, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 47)
  - Poverty, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 48)
  - Productivity Indicators, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 49)
  - Public Hearings, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Report to the People, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Report to the People, 1997-1998 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Report to the People, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Republican Watch, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Senate Wrap-Up, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Small Business, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 7-8)
  - Small Business, 2001-2002 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 1992-1999 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 15-17)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee, undated (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee Correspondence, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee Expenses, undated (Box 70, Folder 23-24)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee Heilman Pavement Specialties, 1996-1998 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Small Business Compliance Advisory Committee Notes, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - State Ethics Commission, 1997-2001 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - State and Local Government, 1994-1998 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - State Legislative Questionnaire, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Reforming Taxes, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Taxes, 1995-1998 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Taxes, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Tax Data Campaigns, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, News, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 35)
- Correspondence/Notes, 1952-2001; VI.
  Marilyn Skolnick was an active member in many communities, the City of Pittsburgh, and the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. As an active community member, Skolnick generated various levels of correspondence. The correspondence, publications, and handwritten notes by Marilyn Skolnick in this series are related to the environmental and transportation issues found throughout the collection. The Correspondence series dates from 1952 to 2001 is further divided into two subseries.
  - Correspondence, 1952-2001; 1.
    The Correspondence subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject and ranges in date from 1952 to 2001.
    - A1D04, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - American Lung Association, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Collective Bargaining Local 85, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Common Cause, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Congressional, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Corridor H, 2000 (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Environmental Email, 1997-1999 (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - Environmental Email, 1998-2000 (Box 70, Folder 44)
    - Environmental Miscellaneous, 1998-2001 (Box 70, Folder 45)
    - Gulf Science and Technology, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Barbara Hayes, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 47)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 48)
    - Linda Howe, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 49)
    - Jenkins and Quinn, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 50)
    - Larry Joyce, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 51)
    - Paul Kusker, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 52)
    - Legislative, 1990-1994 (Box 70, Folder 53)
    - Lois Liberman, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992-2000 (Box 70, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous Emails, 1999-2000 (Box 70, Folder 56)
    - Monroeville Arts Council, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 57)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), 1984 (Box 70, Folder 58)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), 1987-1993 (Box 70, Folder 59)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), 1994 (Box 70, Folder 60)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), 1995 (Box 70, Folder 61)
    - Pittsburgh International Airport, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 62)
    - Mark Pollock, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 63)
    - Public Transit, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 64)
    - Rachel Carson Woman in Environmental Science Award, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 65)
    - Redevelopment, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 66)
    - Reed, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 67)
    - Representatives, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 68)
    - Retaining Agreement, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 69)
    - Suzzanne Seppi, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 70)
    - Sierra Club, 1993-1997 (Box 70, Folder 71)
    - Bruce Sundquist, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 72)
  - Publications and Notes, 1990-1998; 2.
    This subseries dates from 1990 to 1998 and is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - ACHD Notes, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 73)
    - Biographical Information, undated (Box 70, Folder 74)
    - Environmental Notes, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 75)
    - Environmental Notes, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 76)
    - General Notes, 1990-1995 (Box 70, Folder 77)
    - General Notes, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 78)
    - General Notes, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 79)
    - General Notes, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 80-81)
    - General Notes, undated (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
    - Land Disturbance in Monroeville Notes, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Mon/Fayette Notes, 1993-1995 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Political Notes, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Political Notes, undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Public Hearing XXI Notes, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Sierra Club Notes, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Publication, Abstract, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Publication, Stakeholder, undated (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Publication, The Evolution of Public Involvement, undated (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Resumes, undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Skolnick Resume, undated (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Transportation Notes, undated (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Audio-Visual Material, 1987-2009; VII.
  Marilyn Skolnick was an active follower of local and national events and trends concerning environmentalism, transportation, and the intersection of the two subjects. As such, she amassed a large amount of audio-visual material dealing with these issues. The material in the series includes primarily video cassettes, many of which are compilation tapes of news reports and local area meetings. There are also audio cassettes of Transportation Research Board meetings. The Audio-Visual Material series dates from 1987 to 2009 and is further divided into two subseries.
  - VHS Tapes, 1987-2009; 1.
    The VHS Tapes subseries is arranged chronologically and dates from 1987 to 2009, with additional undated material.
    - 1987 primary election; Water & You; Tiger in Your Tank; Hardworking Women; Alaska Refuge of Refuse; DEP Municipal Refuse Regulations; Candidates night, 11/19/87; Monroeville landfill problems, 11/4/87 (Box 72, Item 1)
    - Association of American Railroads, "David's Run", 1987 (Box 72, Item 2)
    - Landfill public hearing and Gateway Auditorium; Citizen of the Year; Recycling- Watch Your Waste; Peacelinks, 2/3/88; Agriculture, 4/6/88 (Box 72, Item 3)
    - African art; Chamber of Commerce- Muni Waste; Landfill- Monroeville's #2 Problem, 6/7/88; The Ashland Oil Spill, 7/6/88; Landfill committee, 7/15/88 (Box 72, Item 4)
    - Cronkite- Environment, 6/11/88 (Box 72, Item 5)
    - Landfill committee meeting, 7/28/88; Marilyn Candler; Acid rain, 10/19/88; Hazmet, 11/10/88; Shoppers alert, 12/7/88 (Box 72, Item 6)
    - Recycling, 1/4/89; Clean water, 2/1/89; Feeder transit system, 3/1/89; Candidates Night Gateway Auditorium, 4/6/89; Candidates Night Gateway Auditorium, 4/27/89 (Box 72, Item 7)
    - Household waste, 5/3/89; Emergency in Monroeville, 6/14/89; Recycling (Gossett), 8/30/89; Clean air, 10/5/89; Kane Hospital, 11/15/89, 12/6/89; Monroeville Mayor Elect, 12/13/89 (Box 72, Item 8)
    - New PAT fare structure, 1/2/90; Earth Day, 3/7/90; Pesticides, Earth Day, 3/7/90; Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 8/15/90; Toxic Production, 9/12/90 (Box 72, Item 9)
    - CBS Clean Air Bill; ABC Energy policy, 8/31/90; To Save the Planet, 10/7/90; Race to Save the Planet, 10/9/90 (Box 72, Item 10)
    - Frontline rain forest, 9/19/90, 9/20/90, 9/21/90; Moyer global dumping, 10/2/90; Night Live lawn care, 5/10/91; Focus on Issues PAT: Alaska Wildlife Reserve, 3/6/96; Stakeholders, 9/11/96 (Box 72, Item 11)
    - Gateway I & II, 10/27/90; Waste environment, 12/12/90; Waste environment, 1/2/91; Public transit: Your Import Investment, 1/2/91; Martin O'Malley, 2/6/91; Alcosan, 3/6/91; Crisis in Transit, 5/1/91; Crisis in transit, 5/29/91; Lawn care, 6/6/91; Citizen Action, Greenpeace, Clean Water Action (Box 72, Item 12)
    - "The Editors: Swep Davis", 1991 (Box 72, Item 13)
    - Hazardous waste incineration, 8/14/91; Hazardous waste II, 8/2/91; Pollution hotspots, 9/10/91; Candidates Night in Allegheny County, 10/10/91; Incineration in Germany, 11/13/91; Wetlands, 1/8/92; Transportation funding problems, 2/12/92; Incineration of hazardous waste, 3/4/92 (Box 72, Item 14)
    - Candidates Night, 4/2/92 (Box 72, Item 15)
    - Garden Grows, 4/8/92; CCC's, 5/13/92; PAT Bargins, 6/10/92; Rio Summit, 7/8/92; PAT Budget cuts, 8/5/92 (Box 72, Item 16)
    - Emissions Trading Conference, 12/8-9/92 (Box 72, Item 17)
    - Environmental issues, 6/2/92; WQED Moyers listening to Americans, 6/2/92 (Box 72, Item 18)
    - Race to Save the Planet, 10/10/92, 10/11/92; Smutty City, 8/26/92; Power Line, "Too Good to be True," 9/2/92 (Box 72, Item 19)
    - Landfill expansion impact on Monroeville, 10/7/92; Social issues, 12/10/92; Neville Island, 1/6/93; Judging the Judges, 3/10/93 (Box 72, Item 20)
    - Focus on Issues, 5/12/93; Candidates Night, 5/93; Landfill ordinance hearing, 5/12/93 (Box 72, Item 21)
    - NAFTA, 7/7/93; LEAD, 8/9/93; NAFTA, 10/13/93; PAT- McNeil and Brown; Yarnell, 1/5/94; BLAHA, 2/2/94; Dear or Deer, 8/10/94 (Box 72, Item 22)
    - Focus on Issues: Mon Valley Express, 4/13/94; Inspection and Maintenance, 6/2/94; Mon Valley Express PRD, 8/16/94; Mon Fayette another view, 9/7/94; Fish and wildlife, Mon Valley Express, 10/12/94; Rick McLey, 11/2/94; Monroeville future, 12/7/94 (Box 72, Item 23)
    - Annual Pittsburgh Chemical Day, Forum, "Responsible Care: Fact or Fiction?", 1993 (Box 72, Item 24)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission, "Choosing a Future", 1993 (Box 72, Item 25)
    - Center for Neighborhood Technology, "Transportation, Environmental Justice and Social Equality," 11/16-18/94 (Box 72, Item 26)
    - Credit Bureau counseling, 1/3/94; PAT service, 2/8/95; Amer. Chestnut, 5/10/95; Ozone on Editors, 6/23/95; Pittsburgh Zoo, 7/12/95; The Ozone Problem, 8/16/95; Medicare revisions, 9/3/95; Just Harvest, 11/15/95 (Box 72, Item 27)
    - Just Harvest, 11/15/95; Pollution prevention, 12/95; The Editors- Clean the Air, 5/24/96; Paying for college education, 6/12/96; Monroeville Arts Festival, 1996; Hazardous waste incineration, 8/7/96 (Box 72, Item 28)
    - Allegheny County/ City of Pittsburgh Task Force on Disabilities, "Small Differences", 1995 (Box 72, Item 29)
    - Petersen, 10/23/96; Pollution Controls: Mon-Fayette Panel, 4/1/96; Mon-Fayette Panel 2, 11/20/96; Benchmarks, 1/15/97; Clean Air, 2/12/97; Urban development problems, 3/19/97; Bird feeders, 4/23/97; Candidate (Mayor), 5/14/97 (Box 72, Item 30)
    - The Editors, 7/16/96 (Box 72, Item 31)
    - CATS Council of Mayors, "Let's Clear the Air", 1996 (Box 72, Item 32)
    - Environmental Information Center, Clean Air Trust, "Can't Breathe", 1/16/97 (Box 72, Item 33)
    - New distribution system, 6/3/97; electric utilities, Part 1, 7/10/97, Part 2; Auctions, 8/13/97; Electric deregulation- David Hughes, 9/24/97; Mayoral night, 10/7/97; BBB, 12/9/97; Mayor Logan, 3/4/98; Link, 3/18 (Box 72, Item 34)
    - "Divided Highway: Pennsylvania Turnpike", 10/22/97 (Box 72, Item 35)
    - Home Rule Charter, 4/29/98; PM10, 6/20/98; 911, 7/22/98; Electricity (Hughes), 8/19/98; Hearing- Urban sprawl, 9/23/98; Urban Sprawl Part 2, 10/20/98 (Box 72, Item 36)
    - Center for Transportation and the Environment, "Wildlife Ecology and Transportation", 11/17/98 (Box 72, Item 37)
    - Autism-Toresky, 1/19/99; Sprawl- Revitalizing, 2/17/99; Community Food Bank, 3/3/99; Larry Bowen PAT, 4/16/99; Ozone, 5/18/99; Library, 6/1/99; Duquesne- "Right-O-Way," 7/1/99; Slagmount, 8/12/99 (Box 72, Item 38)
    - Council- Timbering Proposal, 6/8/99 (Box 72, Item 39)
    - Dan Hughes, Energy Co-ops, 9/29/99; Y2K, 11/30/99; Recycling, 11/4/99; Duquesne Light, 2/9/00; Storm-waste Water Management, 3/7/00 (Box 72, Item 40)
    - Center for Transportation and the Environment, "Thinking Beyond NEPA: Buidling Better Projects Through Community Involvement", 5/31/00 (Box 72, Item 41)
    - Logging, 5/17/00; Antiques, 9/21/00; Phyllis Armstrong, 12/27/00; Mon-Fayette, 11/9/00 (Box 72, Item 42)
    - Center for Transportation and the Environment, "2001 TRB Annual Meeting, Demonstration Session on State-of-the-Art Public Involvement Techniques", 3/01 (Box 72, Item 43)
    - Turnpike funding, 2/13/03 (Box 72, Item 44)
    - Longwall mining, 8/20/03; Amnesty International, 9/24/03; LWV Comm. on Clean Elections, 10/22/03; Marilyn unnecessary way, 12/3/03; Water scarcity problem, 1/14/04; Household hazardous waste, 2/4/04 (Box 72, Item 45)
    - NAFTA Reviewed, 3/10/04; Susan Parker, 4/21/04; STU Strickland, 5/12/04; GAP diesel pollution, 7/14/04 (Box 72, Item 46)
    - Neville Island Good Neighbor Committee Meeting, 7/15/04 (Box 72, Item 47)
    - Candidates Forum Part 1, 8/11/04, Part 2, 9/15/04; Transit funding/mining, 10/13/04; National forests, 11/23/04 (Box 72, Item 48)
    - WalMart/Marilyn, 8/9/05; Transit, 9/19/05; Maglev, 10/25/05; Van pooling, 1/10/06 (Box 73, Item 1)
    - Land use, 1/27/05; Mon-Fayette Panel, 2/15/05; Voyager program, 7/6/05; WalMart, 7/12/05 (Box 73, Item 2)
    - Billboards, 2/8/06; Great Outdoors West, 3/15/06; Meals on Wheels, 5/24/06 (Box 73, Item 3)
    - Alaskan Wilderness League, 6/21/06; American Lung Association, 7/18/06; Mon-Fayette wake, 8/9/06; Transit funding, 10/24/06; New chairman of the Chamber of Commerce, 1/17/06 (Box 73, Item 4)
    - Merton House, 2/20/07; Diesel reduction, 4/12/07; Green building, 10/9/07; Dave McGuill, 5/20/07; Home insulation, 7/10/07; Transit funding, 8/21/07 (Box 73, Item 5)
    - Alcasan, 11/14/07; 12/13/07; Turtle Creek watershed, 12/6/08 (Box 73, Item 6)
    - Candidates night, 3/12/08; Rendell Part 1, 5/17/08, Part 2 and 3, 8/6/08 (Box 73, Item 7)
    - Library, 12/15/09; O'Donnel interview, 10/15/08; Water, 4/10; Candidate night, 4/21/09; Sustain Monroeville, 5/25/09; Clean Water Action, 6/30/09 (Box 73, Item 8)
    - Bill Moyers Report, "Trading Democracy", undated (Box 73, Item 9)
    - Center for Transportation and the Environment, "Examining the Planning and Environmental Provisions of the Next ISTEA", undated (Box 73, Item 10)
    - Department of Transportation, "Transportation Options… The Choice is Yours", undated (Box 73, Item 11)
    - EPP Project Course, "Issues in Bulk Mail: First Presentation", undated (Box 73, Item 12)
    - Focus, Billy Dillon, Schauley, undated (Box 73, Item 13)
    - Hazelwood coke oven incident, undated (Box 73, Item 14)
    - "Hometown Hunger", undated (Box 73, Item 15)
    - IFC Incorporated, "Meeting the Public, Version II", undated (Box 73, Item 16)
    - "Laid to Waste: A Chester Neighborhood Fights for Its Future", undated (Box 73, Item 17)
    - Poster Project for a Sustainable U.S. Environment, "Immigration by the Numbers", undated (Box 73, Item 18)
    - "Right in Our Own Backyards", undated (Box 73, Item 19)
    - "The Role of Transit in Creating Livable Metropolitan Communities", undated (Box 73, Item 20)
    - "Save Our Land, Save Our Towns", undated (Box 73, Item 21)
    - Skolnick Mon-Fayette, undated (Box 73, Item 22)
    - Surface Transportation Policy Project, "Getting There", undated (Box 73, Item 23)
    - University of California Transportation Center, "Boulevards: Good Streets for Good Cities", undated (Box 73, Item 24)
    - University of California Transportation Center, "Clean Air Alternatives", undated (Box 73, Item 25)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 73, Item 26)
  - Audio Cassettes, 1994-1996; 2.
    The Adio Cassettes subseries is arranged chronologically and dates from 1994 to 1996, with additional undated material.
    - Transportation Research Board, "Public Involvement and ISTEA: "Where Do We Go From Here?,"" Tape 1, January 1994 (Box 73, Item 27)